theforce.net 2019-07-29

# TheForce.net: Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY 

1\. INTRODUCTION TF.N LLC (“TFN” or “we”) owns Theforce.net, which provides a collection of online services, including, without limitation, various communication tools, message boards, social networking features, personalized content and branded programming, and any other features, content or applications offered from time to time by TFN, including when the Services are accessed via the Internet, mobile or other device. 

As set forth in our Terms of Use the Services are general audience sites, are not targeted to children, and TFN does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age 

This Privacy Policy applies to each visitor to and user of the Services (individually “User” and collectively, “Users”), including both those who use some of the Services without being registered (“Visitors”) and those who have registered with one of more of the Services (“Members”) to participate in an activity on the Services. By visiting or using the Services you are agreeing to abide by this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy describes TFN’s collection and use of Users’ personal information (e.g., information that identifies a specific person, such as full name or email address) where that information is not otherwise publicly available on the Services. It also describes generally TFN’s practices for handling non-personally identifiable information (e.g., interests, demographics and site usage) to the extent such information is associated with a particular User. 

2\. USER SUBMITTED INFORMATION A. “Registration Information” is the information that Users provide to TFN: (a) to register for certain Services, for example, creating a profile, participating in forums and contests, or participating in chat rooms; or (b) to purchase products or services from or through the Services. Registration Information may include one or more of the following: date of birth, email address, first name, and time zone. 

B. “Profile Content” consists of information Members may choose to add to their member profile, including a Member’s profile picture or avatar, user name, vanity URL, stated location, gender, online addresses, interests, social media contact information (i.e., facebook name, twitter name, and the like) and free-form content such as a Member’s Bio, friends, photo albums, signature, and similar information. A Member’s Profile Content is always public and available to anyone, including other users, search engines, advertisers, third-party application developers, and anyone else with access to the Services. Profile Content may be displayed in search results both on the Services and on external search engines. 

C. “Public Site Content” consists of information you disclose in public areas of the Services, such as your Profile Content, message boards, chat rooms and other community areas. Please be aware that Public Site Content is always public and available to anyone, including other users, search engines, advertisers, third-party application developers, and anyone else with access to the Services. Public Site Content may be displayed in search results both on the Services and on external search engines. 

D. “Correspondence” consists of information you disclose when you contact TFN, for example, for customer service purposes. 

3\. TFN COLLECTED INFORMATION When users access the Services, we may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about those visits. For example, in order to permit your connection to the Services, our servers receive and record information about your computer and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information. If you access the Services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device or other transactional information for that device in order to serve content to it. We also may use cookies and other tracking technologies (including browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe Flash technology including cookies), which are comprised of small bits of data that often include an anonymous unique identifier. Websites send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer so the website can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that site. We may use these technologies to collect and store information about your usage of the Services, including your actions while using the Services, such as pages you have visited, search queries you have run, advertisements you have seen, as well as other anonymous, non-personally identifiable information. TFN may also use cookies and similar tools to relate your use of the Services to personal information obtained from you or a third party. 

Third parties that support the Services by serving advertisements or providing services, such as allowing users to share content or tracking aggregate site usage statistics, may also use these technologies to collect similar information. TFN does not control these third-party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies. 

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information. Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, including cookies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe’s website. Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features or personalization available through the Services. 

To improve the quality of the Services, we may supplement the information we collect with information from third parties. If you access the Services through a third-party connection or log-in, we may also collect your user ID and/or user name associated with that third-party service, or any information you have made public in connection with that service or which the third party shares with partner services. 

4\. USE AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION We only share your non-public personal information with non-affiliated third parties when we believe sharing is permitted by you or authorized by this Privacy Policy. 

We use the information we collect from and about Users for the following purposes: 

A. To provide and manage the Services. We use the information we collect from and about Users to provide the Services and features to you including to measure and improve those services and features, to personalize your experience by delivering relevant content, advertising and marketing messages, to allow you to participate in message boards, contests or promotions, to enable you to communicate and share with other users, and to provide you with customer support and respond to inquiries. We may use aggregated, anonymous data about use of and activity on the Services to assist us in this regard and such data is not subject to this Privacy Policy. 

B. To allow third-party service providers to assist us in providing and managing the Services. TFN may make your non-public personal information available to certain third-party service providers, such as contractors, agents or sponsors, who help us manage or provide the Services. These outside service providers are required to protect non-public personal information entrusted to them and not use it for any other purpose than the specific service they are providing to TFN. 

C. To allow other Users to find you. In order to locate Members that a User may already know in the physical world and/or want to get to know in the online world, TFN allows Users to search for Members using information the User already knows, such as username and identifies users matching that search information. 

D. To deliver relevant advertising. We may use the information you provide to us, and information we collect about your use of the Services through cookies and other technologies, to assist us in delivering you relevant ads when you visit the Services. We may work with third-party advertising networks and advertisers who help deliver these ads to you. We do not share your non-public personal information with these third parties, but we may share anonymized or aggregated information with them to improve the relevancy of the ads you see on the Services. As noted above, these third-party advertising networks and advertisers may also use cookies and similar technologies to collect and track non-personally identifiable information such as demographic information, aggregated information, and Internet activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests. 

E. To contact you. TFN may periodically send promotional materials (e.g., newsletters) or notifications related to the Services to the email address you provided to us at registration or to your account. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials from TFN, you can follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. There are certain service notification emails that you may not opt-out of as long as you are a Member, such as notifications of changes to the Services or policies. 

F. To protect the rights of TFN and our users. There may be instances when TFN may disclose user information without providing notice or choice, including situations where TFN has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of TFN, our employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of users of the Services or members of the public; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the law or legal process. 

G. To complete a merger or sale of assets. If TFN sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, TFN may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction. 

5\. INDIVIDUAL RIGHTS IN THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA If you are located in the European Economic Area, you may seek confirmation regarding whether TFN is processing personal information about you, request access to your personal information and ask that we correct, amend or delete your personal information. Please note that this is in regard to your personal information, not content you have posted to our sites. 

If applicable law provides you the right to request access to, (receive) port, object to or restrict processing, seek rectification or request erasure of personal information held about you by TFN, you may do so, as applicable, through controls on TFN sites or by contacting TFN directly. To protect your privacy, TFN will endeavor to take commercially reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to or making any changes to your personal information. 

6\. MEANS OF NOTICE This Privacy Policy is the primary means by which TFN provides you with notice about its collection and use of your personal information. TFN will not use your personal information in a manner different from what is described in this Privacy Policy without your permission. 

7\. PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES AND ACCEPTANCE RSI may change this Privacy Policy at any time and the changes will become effective as noted on the policy. You are responsible for checking periodically for changes and your continued use of the Services after the Effective Date indicates your acceptance of the new Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy was last revised on May 24, 2018. 

The Effective Date of this Privacy Policy is May 25, 2018. 

8\. LOCATION OF DATA The Services are hosted in the United States. If you are a User located outside the United States, you understand and consent to having any personal information you provide transferred to and processed in the United States. U.S. data protection and other relevant laws may not be the same as those in your jurisdiction. As a result, please read this Privacy Policy with care. 

9\. LINKED WEBSITES OR SERVICES The Services may also be linked to sites or services operated by third parties, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, contests, or applications developed and maintained by third parties. TFN is not responsible for the Privacy practices of any such third parties, and once you leave the Services via a link, enable a third-party service, or click an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third-party site. 

10\. SECURITY TFN uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard user information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. 

11\. CONTACT US If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact TFN via email at webmaster@theforce.net or write to us at: 

Lidji Dorey & Hooper  
500 N. Akard  
Suite 3500  
Dallas, TX 75201
